ULADZIMIR PRYHAZHANAU

iOS Developer



Summary

I am based in Warsaw, Poland and I really am passionate about things I do. Right now I have been developing iOS applications for more than 4 years. I strive to be a high performing and team-work oriented specialist. I am Interested in participating in development of amazing products. I Always ready to work hard to achieve high results in development workflow and product quality.

Education

Institute of Business and Management of Technologies

Information Resource Management

2017-2022

Work Experiences

Andersen Lab

iOS Developer

Sep 2022 - Present

Responsibilities

- Working in huge cross-functional development team with complex structure on high-loaded transportation product (inDrive).
- Reviewing client requirements, wireframes, and designs for technical feasibility. MVP estimations.
- Improving product quality, code reviews, writing unit tests and collaborating with QA team on implementing automation testing.

Key tech stack

Swift	Objective-C	UDF	DF Swinject		XCoordinator	
SnapKit	MapKit	CoreMoti	on Crasl	nlytics	Fastlan	е

Constanta

iOS Developer

May 2020 - Aug 2022

Responsibilities

- Developing and maintaining native iOS/MacOS secured messenger application with e2e data transfer encryption.
- Maintaining team work and delivering new features from discussing to product.
- ${\boldsymbol{\cdot}}$ Identifying, analyzing, and solving software bugs and issues.
- · CI/CD process maintaining.

Key tech stack

Swift	Swift Objective-C Cle		Clea	lean Swift Purel		yout Co		coaAsyncSocket	
CryptoKit AVFoundation		WebRTC Native		Realm		Fastlane			
CallKit	F	irebase	AWS	Sentry	,				

Contact

• Warsaw, Poland

+48 514777861

∨prigozhanov@gmail.com

in/prigozhanov

Skills

- · Swift
- · Objective-C
- UDF
- Clean Swift
- MVVM
- VIPER
- Git
- GitFlow
- Fastlane
- CI/CD Pipelines
- Unit Testing
- · Design Patterns

Languages

- English B2
- Polish A2
- Russian Native

Work Experiences

EPAM Systems

Junior iOS Developer

Jun 2019 - May 2020

Responsibilities

- Developing utility application for consolidate, streamline the tracking devices installation process in trucking industry.
- Participating in training programs and self-study to build a foundational understanding of iOS development principles.

Key tech stack

Swift MVVM MapKit CoreLocation Fastlane Firebase

EPAM Systems

Junior Test Automation Engineer

Aug 2017 - Jun 2019

Responsibilities

- Developing and maintaining automated test scripts written on Java and JavaScript using Appium.
- Analyzing test results to identify defects, classify their severity.

Key tech stack

Java Javascript Appium CodeceptJS